guilty: adj. 犯罪的，违法的, tolerant: adj. 宽容的
Lesson 11, not guilty. Customs officers are quite tolerant these days. But they can still stop you
第11课，无罪。如今，海关官员非常宽容。但是他们仍然可以阻止你
declare: v.   申报
when you are going through the green channel and have nothing to declare. Even really honest people
当您经过绿色频道并且无需声明时。甚至非常诚实的人
guilty: adj. 犯罪的，违法的, hardened: adj. 有经验的, professional: adj. 职业的，专业的, smuggler: n.   走私者
are often made to feel guilty. The hardened professional smuggler, on the other hand,
通常会感到内gui。另一方面，坚强的专业走私者
is never troubled by such feelings. Even if he has 500 gold watches hidden in his suitcase.
从来没有被这种感觉困扰。即使他的手提箱里有500张金表。
When I returned for Mabraud recently, a particularly efficient young customs officer clearly
当我最近返回马布劳德时，一位特别有效的年轻海关官员显然
declare: v.   申报, smuggler: n.   走私者
regarded me as a smuggler. Have you anything to declare? He asked, looking me in the eye.
把我视为走私者。您有什么要声明的吗？他问，看着我。
confidently: adv. 自信地
No, I answered confidently. Would you mind unlocking this suitcase, please?
不，我自信地回答。您介意解锁此手提箱吗？
Single quote dot. Not at all, I answered. The officer went through the case with great care.
单引号点。一点也不，我回答。军官非常谨慎地处理了案件。
dreadful: adj. 可怕的，一团糟的
All the thing I had packed so carefully were soon in a dreadful mess. I felt sure I would never be
我所仔细的所有东西很快就陷入了可怕的混乱之中。我确定我永远不会
able to close the case again. Suddenly, I saw the officers face light up. He had spotted a tiny
能够再次关闭案件。突然，我看到军官面对面。他发现了一个很小的
pounce: v.   猛抓，扑住, sarcastically: adv. 讽刺地
bottle at the bottom of my case and he pounced on it with delight. Perfume. EH? He asks sarcastically.
瓶子在我箱子的底部，他高兴地猛扑了它。香水。嗯？他讽刺地问。
declare: v.   申报, exempt: adj. 被免除的, duty: n.   税
You should have declared that. Perfume is not exempt from import duty. But it isn't Perfume,
您应该宣布这一点。香水不能免除进口义务。但这不是香水，
gel: n.   凝胶, mixture: n.   混合物
I said. It's hair gel. Then I added with a smile. It's a strange mixture I make myself.
我说。这是头发凝胶。然后我笑了笑。我自己做的是一种奇怪的混合物。
unscrew: v.   拧开
As I expected, he did not believe me. Try it. I said encouragingly. The officer unscrewed the cap
正如我所期望的，他不相信我。尝试一下。我鼓舞人心。军官推开了帽子
nostril: n.   鼻孔
and put the bottle to his nostrils. He was greeted by an unpleasant smell which convinced him that I
并把瓶子放在他的鼻孔上。他被一种令人不愉快的气味迎接了他，这使他说服了我
chalk: n.   粉笔
was telling the truth. A few minutes later, I was able to hurry away with precious chalk marks on my
在说实话。几分钟后，我能够用宝贵的粉笔标记在我的
baggage: n.   行李
baggage.
行李。